♪I defy heaven, fate,
and so-called immortality♪
♪At last you say
we've been apart too long♪
♪Unwilling, unyielding, I won't let go♪
♪With you, even a dried sea
learns to embrace a stream♪
♪If heaven divides us, I'll reunite us,
with love as our vessel♪
♪If it forbids it, I'll shatter
the absurd Heavenly Dao♪
♪Even if countless stars
turn into my foes♪
♪To grow old with you, we burn
through the end of the long night♪
=Rise Again=
=Episode 18=
How is she?
Based on her pulse,
prolonging her life
has triggered the curse.
Her blood is flowing backward.
This curse
is now accelerating the extraction
of her life essence.
What do we do?
Well...
Find a way!
No matter the cost,
you must bring her back!
There is one way.
But...
It requires the union
of male and female energies,
yin and yang in perfect balance,
to channel spiritual power into her.
I'll step out first.
You two talk it out.
(If I could transfer the curse
onto myself,)
(would Ningxue be safe?)
Su Wubing.
Are you alright?
I'm fine.
What are you doing?
I heard everything Mr. Ye said.
Listen carefully.
Neither of us
is allowed to die.
Master, is this...?
As expected,
his body is terrifyingly strong.
You already sensed me?
After last night,
the pain seems a bit better.
But is the curse still there?
The power I infused into you
can suppress it for now.
But when the time comes...
I believe you.
Ningxue.
So this is why grandpa
didn't want me coming here.
The two of you are together.
(So it is her.)
Su Wubing.
You promised me you'd cure my illness.
Illness?
What illness can't Mr. Ye cure?
My illness?
Only Su Wubing can help with that.
Don't forget...
What kind of illness is it?
So mysterious.
Of course it's...
(After refining the final Cold Marrow,)
(I'm only one step away
from the Heavenly God Realm.)
Xiaonuan.
The Cold Marrow in your body
is almost fully refined.
The rest can be treated
by your grandfather.
Are you already with Lin Ningxue?
Answer me.
Look at me.
I just want to know
was there ever a place for me
in your heart?
Even for a moment?
Xiaonuan.
Ningxue and I are destined.
We can't be separated.
I didn't like you
just because you cured me.
I...
I know.
But my heart belongs only to her.
Am I really not good enough?
Mr. Gu, ever since the tournament,
all major families in Fan City
have started backing the Lin family.
Our stock price...
it's collapsing.
What did you say?
And the reclusive Fang family
seems to be supporting them
from behind as well.
If we still want to take over
the Lin Group,
we might have to...
Say it.
We might have to
make peace with the Lin family.
Seek their help.
What? Get out!
Mr. Gu, why are you so angry?
The Gu family has vast resources.
Why fear a comeback from the Lin family?
If I had known this would happen,
I should've killed Su Wubing
before the tournament.
Mr. Gu.
I've stayed by your side for so long,
loyal and devoted.
So...?
What do you want?
That depends on what you can give me.
If I become Mrs. Gu...
that would be...
How about this.
From now on, you'll manage
the entire Gu Group.
How's that?
Really?
Here's a slap to wake you up.
Mrs. Gu?
Look at yourself.
You dare hit back?
♪I defy heaven, fate,
and so-called immortality♪
♪At last you say
we've been apart too long♪
♪Unwilling, unyielding, I won't let go♪
♪With you, even a dried sea
learns to embrace a stream♪
♪If heaven divides us, I'll reunite us,
with love as our vessel♪
♪If it forbids it, I'll shatter
the absurd Heavenly Dao♪
♪Even if countless stars
turn into my foes♪
♪To grow old with you, we burn
through the end of the long night♪